kiboomu.com 2016-11-03

# PRIVACY POLICY

### Privacy Policy for Kiboomu Kids Songs

Our privacy policy and the privacy of our visitors is very important to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by Kiboomu Kids Songs and how it is used.

This site has never sold this information nor will it ever. All information is used only to gather demographics, statistics, and other metrics to better serve our readers.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Kiboomu Kids Songs does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include :

Amazon.com, Glam Media, iTunes.com

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on the site send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Kiboomu Kids Songs has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

These ad companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to·not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/).  Kiboomu Kids Songs’ privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### Contacting Kiboomu Kids Songs

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [info@kiboomu.com](mailto:info@kiboomu.com)
